gamesting.com 2012-03-20

# Privacy Policy - GameSting.com

Gamesting is committed to providing an entertaining, fun and educational service. Gamesting.com is a property of ItalosMedia "Gamesting". Gamesting respects the privacy concerns of visitors to Gamesting.com. Gamesting does not target its website or services to under 13 year olds, but does take measures to help protect those that happen to be under 13. We take measures to help children protect their privacy while online. For example, we do not ask children to disclose more personal information than is necessary for them to participate in a particular activity. 

**Information we collect**

We may log IP addresses and/or drop cookies and/or flash cookies to prevent abuse of our website and or to provide and or to enhance services. 

**Information that is reasonably necessary**

Gamesting does not require persons under 13 years of age to disclose any more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity as a condition of participation. 

**How we use the information**

We do not retain any personal information beyond the time it is needed. We may use information to ensure that users are in compliance with our terms. Gamesting may disclose information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with Gamesting's property, visitors, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.   
We may sometimes use non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our website, to personalize our visitors' experience or to offer products, programs and services. We may also use this information in the aggregate to analyze website usage, as well as to offer products, programs, or services. 

**Collection of Information and Third-Parties and Sponsors**

We do not disclose personally identifiable information of users under 13 years of age to third parties. We use DoubleClick and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies and Gamesting may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this website and other websites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Third parties and or Gamesting may be placing and reading standard and or flash cookies on your browser and machine, or using web beacons to collect information on the website and in the course of ads being served. We may also share the anonymous information that we collect from you with our business partners or clients so that they may improve their services. Third parties such as advertisers, games companies and or developers may ask for information from you which would be governed by the privacy policy of those other companies in which case they should provide adequate disclosure of their privacy policies to you. We may use anonymous information that we collect from you to improve our services and or to help serve advertising to you. You may manage or opt out of your standard cookies via your web browser and if you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here   
Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, gamesting.com has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

**Security**

We have implemented appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

The contents of this policy may be altered at any time, at our discretion. 

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of gamesting.com then you may contact us at admin@gamesting.com   
Last updated , 10 January 2011 23:02 PCT 

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
